(Sheldon:)It's a children's story.
(Howard:)Oh, no, it isn't.
(Sheldon:)When I was a little boy and got sick,
which was most of the time...
(Sheldon:)...my mother would read it.
(Sheldon:)It's about an Indian princess
who befriends a monkey...
...who was mocked by the other monkeys
because he was different.
(Sheldon:)For some reason,
I related to it quite strongly.
(Penny:)I know the reason.
(Leonard:)We all know the reason.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, what are you getting at?
(Sheldon:)That woman looks exactly like the pictures
of Princess Panchali in the book.
(Sheldon:)How often does one see a beloved
fictional character come to life?
Every year at Comic-Con.
(Howard:)Every day at Disneyland.
(Howard:)You can hire Snow White
to come to your house.
Of course, they prefer it if you have a kid.
(Raj:)Hey, guys. This is Lalita Gupta.
(Raj:)Lalita, this is Leonard and Sheldon
and Howard and Penny.
Isn’t it great? She isn't fat anymore.
(Sheldon:)Forgive me, Your Highness...
(Sheldon:)...for I am but a monkey
and it is in my nature to climb.